module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What liquid did the Mayflower carry the most of?', 
    a: 'Water',
    b: 'Wine',
    c: 'Beer',
    d: 'Honey',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many players are there in a baseball team?', 
    a: 'Ten',
    b: 'Nine',
    c: 'Seven',
    d: 'Twelve',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of Batman\'s son?', 
    a: 'Robin',
    b: 'Dick',
    c: 'Damien',
    d: 'Jason',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What must the alcoholic beverage "Melomel" contain?', 
    a: 'Fruit',
    b: 'Fresh Hops',
    c: 'Barley',
    d: 'Chocolate',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What makes whiskey a "straight" whiskey?', 
    a: 'Made in Kentucky',
    b: 'Over 50% Rye',
    c: 'Aged for 2 Years',
    d: 'Rates a 0 on the Kinsey Scale',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'When did the Cleveland Indians last win the World Series?', 
    a: '2016',
    b: '1926',
    c: '1952',
    d: '1948',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the city of Cleveland named after?', 
    a: 'General Robert Cleveland',
    b: 'General Moses Cleaveland',
    c: 'President Grover Cleveland ',
    d: 'Writer Francis Cleaveland ',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'By what name is Norma Jean Baker more commonly known?', 
    a: 'Madonna',
    b: 'Marilyn Monroe',
    c: 'Cher',
    d: 'Jennifer Lawrence',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following isn\'t a member of the Marx Brothers?', 
    a: 'Groucho',
    b: 'Chipo',
    c: 'Zeppo',
    d: 'Harpo',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'If you were eating "du Barry," what would you be eating?', 
    a: 'Cauliflower Soup',
    b: 'A French Cheese',
    c: 'Grilled Duck ',
    d: 'Smoked Sausage ',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];
